
▀▀█▀▀ █░░█ █▀▀ 　 ▒█▀▀▀ █░░ █▀▀▄ █▀▀ █▀▀█ 　 ▒█▀▀▀█ █▀▀ █▀▀█ █▀▀█ █░░ █░░ █▀▀ ▄ 
░▒█░░ █▀▀█ █▀▀ 　 ▒█▀▀▀ █░░ █░░█ █▀▀ █▄▄▀ 　 ░▀▀▀▄▄ █░░ █▄▄▀ █░░█ █░░ █░░ ▀▀█ ░ 
░▒█░░ ▀░░▀ ▀▀▀ 　 ▒█▄▄▄ ▀▀▀ ▀▀▀░ ▀▀▀ ▀░▀▀ 　 ▒█▄▄▄█ ▀▀▀ ▀░▀▀ ▀▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ ▀▀▀ ▀ 

░█▀▀█ ▒█▀▀█ ▒█▀▀▀ ▒█▄░▒█ ░█▀▀█ 
▒█▄▄█ ▒█▄▄▀ ▒█▀▀▀ ▒█▒█▒█ ▒█▄▄█ 
▒█░▒█ ▒█░▒█ ▒█▄▄▄ ▒█░░▀█ ▒█░▒█ 



Thank you for downloading the Unoffical Game Soundtrack to The Elder Scrolls: Arena! 
Eric Heberling has such a rich and dynamic score that it's my pleasure to make it available to all TES fans.

if you're a regular follower of john nieuwsma and/or mister lonely and are confused, let me explain. i've been facilitating this unofficial 
soundtrack on my youtube channel for awhile and i thought it be appropriate to include a digital download since there's nowhere else to 
find this version on the internet (trust me I looked everywhere. that's why i made this in the first place).

This album is the work of composer eric heberling and i do not own any of it. no official tracklist or album cover was given for these songs so
everything you see is my own creation. what you hear is most definitely not. i will be keeping this soundtrack completely free with no way of 
spending money. i've made this purely for the fans who want access to some sweet music.

you can download arena for free on bethesda's website: https://elderscrolls.bethesda.net/en/arena

i recorded all audio from my version of arena on a dosbox emulator using audacity. prior to my release, the only versions i could find on the
internet had uploaded the midi files, resulting in a smoother, less retro sounding soundtrack. i wanted to listen to the lower-res version i
always heard when i'd play the game. so i made this soundtrack myself to fill that gap.

Included in the complete download are two bonus tracks. "You see a goblin" is an edited version of "dungeon crawling" that includes
more ambience and in-game sound effects to make you feel like you're really exploring an elder scrolls arena dungeon. "Game over" is simply
an extended version of "a Vision Beyond" because I couldn't decide which length i liked better.

i may continue to edit and change things around with this upload depending on anything else i find in the game so don't be alarmed if you
come back to the bandcamp page and there are some new things available.

i may make floppy diskettes with music free to purchase (excluding shipping) in the future.
i like the idea of owning a retro copy of the soundtrack. we'll see if I don't use my blanks for other releases.

TRacklist ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. opening titles /// 
Played in the opening titles and main menu screen.

2. tharn's betrayal /// 
Played during the intro cinematic, in which the narrator explains Tharn's ascension to the throne. The player is also introduced.

3. where dost thou hail ///
Played during the character creation screen.

4. a vision beyond ///
Played during dream sequences or game over screens.

5. dungeon crawling ///
Played inside dungeons, caves, and other such enemy fortresses.

6. the late hours ///
Played during the evening (excluding interior areas).

7. the wandering inn ///
Played upon entering an inn (Version 1)

8. the first seed ///
Played during the day while outdoors in most weather conditions. Includes brief "entry music."

9. blacksmith ///
Played upon entering a blacksmith shop.

10. winter in hammerfell ///
Played outside during winter weather. The music sounds slightly "middle-eastern" 
so I'm assuming it's specific to the region of Hammerfell, but I could be wrong.

11. the audience chamber ///
Played upon entering a palace

12. the mages guild ///
Played upon entering a magic shop, temple, or Mages Guild building. (Version 1).

13. a warm welcome ///
Played upon entering an inn (Version 2). On a sorta unrelated note, this is one of my personal favorites.

14. evening star ///
Played outside during winter weather (Version 2).

15. swimming ///
Played while swimming, duh.

16. foggy afternoon ///
Played outside in foggy weather.

17. arcane arts ///
Played upon entering a magic shop, temple, or Mages Guild building. (Version 2).

18. breaking and entering ///
Played upon breaking into a house.

19. destination reached ///
A collection of jingles played upon entering towns, cities, and other locations.

20. you see a goblin [feat. john nieuwsma] [bonus track] ///
A partially-original composition of mine, in which I take sound effects and music straight from the game to 
create a more eerie, "realistic" dungeon crawling experience.

21. Game over [bonus track] ///
A slightly extended version of "A Vision Beyond" or the death/dream interlude.

22. objective completed ///
Played upon collecting a quest item or making progress in the main story.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------


▒█▀▄▀█ ▀█▀ ▒█▀▀▀█ ▀▀█▀▀ ▒█▀▀▀ ▒█▀▀█ 　 ▒█░░░ ▒█▀▀▀█ ▒█▄░▒█ ▒█▀▀▀ ▒█░░░ ▒█░░▒█ 
▒█▒█▒█ ▒█░ ░▀▀▀▄▄ ░▒█░░ ▒█▀▀▀ ▒█▄▄▀ 　 ▒█░░░ ▒█░░▒█ ▒█▒█▒█ ▒█▀▀▀ ▒█░░░ ▒█▄▄▄█ 
▒█░░▒█ ▄█▄ ▒█▄▄▄█ ░▒█░░ ▒█▄▄▄ ▒█░▒█ 　 ▒█▄▄█ ▒█▄▄▄█ ▒█░░▀█ ▒█▄▄▄ ▒█▄▄█ ░░▒█░░ 

